

Rwego **Patrick**

PROFILE

I have a passion for computer software and electronics and am self-motivated.

I've worked on some projects that have qualified me to be happy with what I do, and my education and expertise have made me an excellent tech developer at my age.

I value being able to accomplish things in a productive workplace!

CONTACT



+25(0) 780 882 838



rwego.patrick.50@gmail.com



Kigali, Rwanda.



https://linkedin.com/in/rwegopatrick/



https://github.com/pattusdev/



https://twitter.com/lapattus

SKILLS

Check my linkedIn

- Udacity Fullstack Nano Degree (Cert.)
- CISCO Network Essential (Cert.)
- CISCO CyberSecurity Essential (Cert.)
- CISCO NDG Linux Unhatched (Cert.)
- CISCO NDG Lunix Essential (Cert.)
- Udemy Python Programming (Cert.)

EDUCATION

Adventist • **University of Central Africa** (AUCA)

Kigali, Rwanda

IPRC Kigali (High School)

Kigali, Rwanda

G.S Remera Rukoma (O' Level)

Kamonyi, Rwanda

Software Engineering Nov/2020-2023

By employing scientific principles, information systems can create effective and competitive information communication systems.

A2. Computer Electronics Jan/2016-Nov/2018

Having completed my final year project, which was an IOT cloud-based project utilizing Firebase, I graduated with expertise in computers and electronics.

Jan/2013-Nov/2015

Excellent experience with boarding institutions that are far from home.

EXPERIENCE

Udacity – ALX-T Alumni

Remote

Lecturer

Kigali, Rwanda

Graduate/2022-Present

I am an Udacity Software Development Graduate and an ALX Certified Full Stack Developer.

KIC School – Lecturer/2019-2020

I have instructed students at Kigali Integrated College in Kabuga who desired a brief course in basic electronics.

Web Developer/2018-2019

I worked as a web developer on the team that developed the e-commerce website, developing scripts and managing social media marketing.

Gilemo.com -**OnlineShopping**

Kigali, Rwanda